Beyond courage, beyond honor.
Hart's War is a drama, war film directed by Gregory Hoblit.
William McNamara is stripped of his freedom in a German POW camp, he's
determined to keep on fighting even from behind enemy lines.
Enlisting the help of a young lieutenant in a brilliant plot against his captors, McNamara
risks everything on a mission to free his men and change the outcome of the war.
Col. William A. McNamara, played by Bruce Willis.
Lt. Thomas W. Hart, played by Colin Farrell.
Lt. Lincoln A. Scott, played by Terrence Howard.
Col. Werner Visser, played by Marcel Iureș.
Staff Sgt. Vic W. Bedford, played by Cole Hauser.
Capt. Peter A. Ross, played by Linus Roache.
Hart's War is a 2002 American war and legal drama film about a World War II
prisoner of war (POW) camp based on the novel by John Katzenbach.
It stars Bruce Willis as Col.
William McNamara and Colin Farrell as Lt.
Thomas Hart.
The film co-stars Terrence Howard, Cole Hauser, and Marcel Iures.
Directed by Gregory Hoblit, the film was shot at Barrandov
Studios in Prague, and released on February 15, 2002.
The film earned mixed reviews, grossing $33.1
million against its $70 million budget.
The film explores themes of escape, world war ii,
prisoner of war, us army, trial.
The tone is emotional.